<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DigiPaws</string>

    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="stop">Stop</string>
     <string name="missing_permission">Permission Missing</string>
    
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="proceed">Proceed</string>
    <string name="buy_20_mins">Purchase 20 minutes</string>
    <string name="desc_sd_overlay">Do you want to buy a 20 minute timewaster for 1 Aura? This purchase will lift off all restrictions from this app or item for the next 20 minutes. </string>
    
    <string name="no_coins_title">Insufficient Aura</string>
    <string name="desc_no_coins_overlay">You have 0 Aura, perform a quest to earn Aura now!</string>
    
    <string name="desc_ex_overlay">Are you sure you want to continue wasting your time?</string>
    
    
    <string name="breathe">Take a deep breath!!!</string>
    <string name="warning_title">Are you sure?</string>

    <string name="notification_accessibility_permission">Accessibilty Services required to run blockers.</string>
     <string name="notification_overlay_permission">This app requires overlay permission to display warning screen each time when a blocked item is found on screen.</string>
    <string name="notification_notif_permission">Notification permission required to receive quest updates.</string>
    <string name="notification_location_permission">Precise Location permission required to track location for this quest.</string>
   <string name="notification_camera_permission">Camera permission required to track position and count reps for this quest.</string>
    
    
    <string name="notification_marathon_title">Marathon Quest in running</string>
    
    
     <string name="select_quest">Select Quest</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="app_desc">DigiPaws is an open-source Android productivity utility designed to help users reduce screen addiction by regulating app usage through a gamified experience. The application offers three distinct modes—Easy, Adventure, and Hard—each with unique features and challenges to promote healthy screen time habits.</string>
    
    <string name="easy_mode">Easy Mode</string>
    <string name="easy_mode_desc">In Easy Mode, DigiPaws provides gentle reminders to help you manage your screen time. When you attempt to access a blocked app, a warning screen appears. If you choose to proceed, a cooldown period starts. After the cooldown, another warning is displayed to remind you of your usage.</string>
    
    <string name="adventure_mode">Adventure Mode</string>
    <string name="adventure_mode_desc">Adventure Mode introduces a gamified experience to control screen time. To access a blocked app, you need Aura. These can be earned by completing quests such as a quick 1 km walk. Each Aura grants 20 minutes of usage time for any blocked app, encouraging physical activity and mindful screen use.</string>
    
    <string name="hard_mode">Hard Mode</string>
    <string name="hard_mode_desc">Hard Mode offers the most stringent control over app usage. In this mode, when you try to open a blocked app, the back button is automatically pressed without any warning or cooldown, preventing access entirely.</string>
    
     <string name="block_vb_title">What do you wish to block?</string>
    <string name="block_shorts_cb">Block Shorts</string>
     <string name="block_comments_cb">Block Comments</string>
     <string name="block_porn_cb">Block Explict Keywords</string>
    <string name="block_vb_desc">Supported Platforms: Youtube, Instagram, Revanced</string>
    
    <string name="anti_uninstall_title">Enter the #TechRehab challenge!</string>
    <string name="anti_uninstall_cb">Activate Anti-Uninstall</string>
    <string name="anti_uninstall_desc">#TechRehab is a 3 week productivity challenge that blocks all uninstall attempts on this app.</string>
     <string name="anti_uninstall_desc_day">days strong!!!</string>
    
    
     <string name="choose_mode_title">Configure Mode</string>
    <string name="choose_mode">Choose Mode</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading</string>
    
    
     <string name="choose_delay_title">How often?</string>
      <string name="choose_delay_desc">This is the cooldown period between each warnings.(ONLY FOR EASY MODE)</string>

    <string name="choose_blocked_apps_title">App Blocker Configuration</string>
    <string name="choose_blocked_apps_desc">Select the apps you wish to block or receive usage warnings for.</string>
    
    <string name="perm_quest_manager_label">Digipaws Quests</string>
    <string name="perm_quest_manager_desc">Allow this app to act as an quest and modify Aura count?</string>


    <string name="pref_category_key_camera" translatable="false">pckc</string>
    <string name="pref_category_title_camera" translatable="false">Camera</string>
    <string name="pref_key_rear_camera_preview_size" translatable="false">rcpvs</string>
    <string name="pref_key_rear_camera_picture_size" translatable="false">rcpts</string>
    <string name="pref_key_front_camera_preview_size" translatable="false">fcpvs</string>
    <string name="pref_key_front_camera_picture_size" translatable="false">fcpts</string>
    
    <string name="marathon_desc">Move out of the above red zone to win this quest. There is no penalty for failing this quest. Do not forget to carry your phone!</string>
    <string name="squats_desc">Simply perform $valuex squats to earn 1 Aura point. You are free to perform this quest in sets of any.Make sure your entire body is visible on camera above. Not working? </string>
    <string name="pushups_desc">Simply perform $valuex pushups to earn 1 Aura point. You are free to perform this quest in sets of any. Make sure your entire body is visible on camera above. Not working? </string>
    <string name="focus_desc">Focus or survival mode blocks all apps except basic needs like calling and SMS for the next 90 minutes. Once focus mode is turned on, it CANNOT be turned off until the timer goes off. Completing this quest brings 1 Aura coin.</string>

    <string name="aura_earned_1">You earned 1 Aura coin</string>
    <string name="tac">By continuing, you agree to our Terms and Conditions</string>

    <string name="accessibility_perm">This app solely depends on Accessibility Permission to block elements. We do not store any of this data on our servers; everything is processed locally. By pressing "Agree," you accept our data usage policy.</string>

    <string name="choose_msg_title">Configure your warning screen</string>

     <string name="battery_optimisation_title">Disable Battery Optimization</string>
    <string name="battery_optimisation_desc">To ensure this app works properly, please disable battery optimization for this app.</string>

    
</resources>