<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DigiPaws</string>

    <string name="marathon_desc">Move out of the above red zone to win this quest. There is no penalty for failing this quest. Do not forget to carry your phone!</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="stop">Stop</string>
     <string name="missing_permission">Permission Missing</string>
    
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="proceed">Proceed</string>
    <string name="buy_20_mins">Purchase 20 minutes</string>
    <string name="desc_sd_overlay">Do you want to buy a 20 minute timewaster for 1 digicoin? This purchase will lift off all restrictions from this app or item for the next 20 minutes. </string>
    
    <string name="desc_ex_overlay">Are you sure you want to continue wasting your time?</string>
    
    
    <string name="breathe">Take a deep breath!!!</string>
    <string name="warning_title">Are you sure?</string>

    <string name="notification_accessibility_permission">Accessibilty Services required to run blockers.</string>
     <string name="notification_overlay_permission">This app requires overlay permission to display warning screen each time when a blocked item is found on screen.</string>
    <string name="notification_notif_permission">Notification permission required to receive quest updates.</string>
    <string name="notification_location_permission">Precise Location permission required to track location for this quest.</string>
    
    
    <string name="notification_marathon_title">Marathon Quest in running</string>
    
    
     <string name="select_quest">Select Quest</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="app_desc">DigiPaws is an open-source Android productivity utility designed to help users reduce screen addiction by regulating app usage through a gamified experience. The application offers three distinct modes—Easy, Adventure, and Hard—each with unique features and challenges to promote healthy screen time habits.</string>
    
    <string name="easy_mode">Easy Mode</string>
    <string name="easy_mode_desc">In Easy Mode, DigiPaws provides gentle reminders to help you manage your screen time. When you attempt to access a blocked app, a warning screen appears. If you choose to proceed, a cooldown period starts. After the cooldown, another warning is displayed to remind you of your usage.</string>
    
    <string name="adventure_mode">Adventure Mode</string>
    <string name="adventure_mode_desc">Adventure Mode introduces a gamified experience to control screen time. To access a blocked app, you need DigiCoins. These can be earned by completing quests such as a quick 1 km walk. Each DigiCoin grants 20 minutes of usage time for any blocked app, encouraging physical activity and mindful screen use.</string>
    
    <string name="hard_mode">Hard Mode</string>
    <string name="hard_mode_desc">Hard Mode offers the most stringent control over app usage. In this mode, when you try to open a blocked app, the back button is automatically pressed without any warning or cooldown, preventing access entirely.</string>
    
     <string name="block_vb_title">What do you wish to block?</string>
    <string name="block_shorts_cb">Block Shorts</string>
     <string name="block_comments_cb">Block Comments</string>
     <string name="block_porn_cb">Block Explict Keywords</string>
    <string name="block_vb_desc">Supported Platforms: Youtube, Instagram, Revanced</string>
    
     <string name="choose_mode_title">Configure Mode</string>
    <string name="choose_mode">Choose Mode</string>
    
     <string name="choose_delay_title">How often?</string>
      <string name="choose_delay_desc">This is the cooldown period between each warnings.(ONLY FOR EASY MODE)</string>

    <string name="choose_blocked_apps_title">App Blocker Configuration</string>
    <string name="choose_blocked_apps_desc">Select the apps you wish to block or receive usage warnings for.</string>
    
    <string name="perm_quest_manager_label">Digipaws Quests</string>
    <string name="perm_quest_manager_desc">Allow this app to act as an quest and modify digicoin counts?</string>

</resources>